tastingtable.com 2017-01-28

# FAQ | Tasting Table

#### What is Tasting Table's Editorial Policy?

Tasting Table's recommendations are selected by our editorial staff and trusted contributors. We don't rely on press releases or hearsay to determine what merits mention. We personally test every bar, restaurant and recipe we recommend, to ensure that we serve you only honest and objective content.

Most important, our taste is not for sale. Brands and establishments cannot pay to be recommended by Tasting Table. Our advertisers are featured in obvious positions on our website and emails, because we believe your trust is essential to our success.

If you're a business owner or publicist or just an ardent fan of a local establishment, you can suggest it to our editors. See our Contact page for information by clicking [here](http://tastingtable.com/footer/national/contact.htm).

#### What is Tasting Table's Restaurant Coverage Policy?

Before recommending a restaurant, new or old, a Tasting Table editor or contributor always visits the establishment at least once, but often several times. The editor or contributor typically dines unannounced and always pays for his or her own meal. If Tasting Table editors dine at a restaurant that we do not feel is worth recommending, we simply do not write about it.

#### What Is a Partner Tip/Advertorial Email?

Occasionally we'll send you a Partner Tip email from one of our advertisers. These advertorial features are clearly marked as such by the email's subject line and a note at the top of the article itself. The content of these Partner Tips is paid for by our sponsors, and does not reflect the opinions of the Tasting Table editorial staff. Hey, we've gotta eat too.

#### What Does the "Tested & Approved" Banner Mean?

Every recipe we publish has been carefully tested by our food editor in the Tasting Table [Test Kitchen](http://tastingtable.com/kitchen) to ensure that each step of the process works smoothlyand that the final product tastes great. (It's a hard job, but someone's got to do it.) Keep an eye out for the "Tested & Approved" banner at the top right corner of recipe pages on [TastingTable.com.](http://www.tastingtable.com/)

#### What is Tasting Table's Privacy Policy?

TDT Media Inc. takes the private nature of your personal information very seriously. This privacy policy describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit our Web site and/or register for our daily email. Please read this notice carefully.

**Personal Information:** To receive your Tasting Table emails, we require your email address. So that we may provide you with additional services, we may also request your name and zip code. Tasting Table does not collect any other personally identifiable information that you do not expressly provide. Tasting Table will never sell, rent or share your personal information, including your email address, with any third parties for marketing purposes without your express permission. Tasting Table may share your personal information for the purpose of delivering our email to you or as required by law.

**Nonpersonal Information:** We may also request nonpersonally identifiable information, such as annual income, shopping preferences or age, also known as demographic and profile data, though this information is optional. We may use this data to improve our site and/or tailor your experience at our site, showing you or delivering to you by email content that we think might be of interest to you, and displaying content according to your preferences. We may also share this information with others, such as advertisers interested in advertising in Tasting Table emails or on our site, in aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the information will not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any other person.

**Usage Information:** In addition to collecting personal and nonpersonal information, Tasting Table may also collect nonpersonal, aggregated information about subscribers' use of our site. This information is not personally identifiable and will only be used to find out how subscribers use our service and site. For example, this information will tell us how much time users spend on our site, from which other sites subscribers came, and to what other sites subscribers go. The collection of this information allows us, among other things, to prepare for traffic load demands and to efficiently deliver your emails.

**Review and Access:** Upon your request, we will provide you with a summary of the information we collect about you. You will have an opportunity to correct, update or modify this information.

**Choice/Opt-Out:** If we ever send you information by email concerning new products or services that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an email address by which you may request no future notices.

**Third-Party Advertising:** Some of the ads appearing on our website may be delivered to you by our web advertising partner or partners. Information about your visit to a partner site or sites, such as the number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you. For more information about our advertising partner or partners, cookies and how to opt out, please contact us at [concierge@TastingTable.com](mailto:concierge@TastingTable.com).

**Tracking:** Like most sites, Tasting Table makes use of browser "cookies." Cookies are small text files placed on your computer's hard disk by our server. They allow us to quickly check your status as a subscriber and facilitate access to your preferences. Tasting Table will never use cookies to retrieve information from a computer that is unrelated to our site or services. Tasting Table also uses transparent GIF images. We use these images to track the emails that we send out.

**Third-Party Cookies:** In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

**Links to Other Sites:** As part of the service, Tasting Table may create links allowing you to access third-party sites. Tasting Table is not responsible for the content that appears on those sites and does not endorse these sites. Please consult those sites' individual privacy policies in order to determine how they treat user information.

**Security:** All information described above is stored on restricted database servers.

**Modification to This Policy:** Tasting Table may change this policy, but we'll post any changes here, so be sure to check back for future information.

**Contact Us:** If you have any questions about this policy or our site in general, please contact [concierge@TastingTable.com](mailto:concierge@tastingtable.com).

#### How do I manage my account?

Simply visit [TastingTable.com/manage](http://tastingtable.com/manage) and enter your email address at the top.

#### How do I manage my To-Dos list?

If you're near your computer, visit [TastingTable.com](http://tastingtable.com/) and click the red "To-Dos" button in the navigation bar at the top right to access your To-Dos list. If you're on the move, you'll want to download our iPhone application, [Tasting Table To-Go](http://itunes.apple.com/us/app/tasting-table-to-go/id413109890?mt=8), to manage your list from your mobile phone.
